Beautiful wife
Do you like potatoes?
Of course
Potatoes are delicious
I love to eat too
I still remember
When you cook Potato Stew with Meat
My grandson eats it like this, bite after bite.
They think it's delicious.
My grandson said it was delicious.
Eat an extra bowl of rice
Remember you told me
Potatoes are good for people with bad stomachs
People with acid reflux
It was good for them to eat
Yes
I have a little trick
People with bad stomach
Let your stomach
be obedient
I'll tell you in a minute.
Hu Naiwen starts his lecture
I am your old friend, Doctor Hu
I want to share this episode with you
1. Have you got acid reflux? Eat potatoes and it will help reduce acidity
2. One Post-Workout Eating Method to Build Muscle and Stabilize Blood Sugar
3. Muscle Cramps Are No Small Matter! Eat This Way to Replenish Potassium and Prevent Pain
4. Eating Sprouted Potatoes by Mistake Can Be Fatal — 2 Tips to Prevent Potatoes from Sprouting
5. Sweet Potato vs. Potato: How to Choose for Weight Loss and Heart Health
Have you got acid reflux? Eat potatoes and it will help reduce acidity
Potatoes can
nourish the bǔyǎng zhōng qì (Transliteration) and strengthen the body
For those who are overworked or weak
It is a mild and practical ingredient
In order not to make you too tired
Have a snack first
This is delicious
Made with potatoes and pumpkin
Very fragrant
Good
Potatoes can be turned
into mashed potatoes
Pumpkin can be turned into pumpkin puree
We can come to like you.
These two together
It's really delicious
Awesome
I know
you like this.
Potatoes are the stars of the starch world
Not only contains rich starch
It also has an ingredient
Called mucopolysaccharides
Can protect the gastric mucosa
Especially suitable for people with poor stomach
and acid reflux
Eating it often can reduce acid reflux
It is no exaggeration to say
that it is a natural antacid.
So awesome
Tell everyone quickly
Tell me your secret
People with bad stomach
How to eat it?
I'll teach you a trick
A glass of potato juice with honey
Let the stomach be obedient
You prepare 300 grams
of fresh potatoes
After washing, cut into pieces with skin
Then make juice
Do not peel
Drink about 180 ml each time
You can add a little honey to taste
Drink it warm and comfortable
Remember this
This must be freshly juiced and drunk immediately
Don't say it was juiced
and then left in the fridge for a long time
If you leave it for too long, it will ferment.
What about people with upset stomachs?
Can drink more?
No
You can't drink too much
Potatoes contain a substance
called solanine
This alkaloid
There is a slight toxicity
Although the amount is not much.
But drinking too much?
It will make body very uncomfortable
Who is not suitable?
Not suitable for children to drink
Because their digestive system
is not fully developed yet
Adults can just drink once in a while.
Drinking in moderation is the most important thing
Taking care of your stomach doesn't mean drinking a lot
One Post-Workout Eating Method to Build Muscle and Stabilize Blood Sugar
Photographer says
He is now an uncle.
Dà shū (Transliteration)is not a dà yíng (Transliteration)
Is Dà shū (Transliteration)
Uncle
Uncle is uncle.
He said that in order to control his weight
Preventing the three highs
So he went to the gym.
Gym doing fitness exercises
He feels hungry after exercising.
He goes to the convenience store to eat a lot of food
Eat a lot
Calories is back
Photographer
You want
Eliminate your fat
Increase your muscles
Stabilize your blood sugar
You can go to the supermarket
Go buy a good item
Do you know what it is?
Baked potatoes
Delicious and convenient
Beautiful wife
I want to ask you a question
Potatoes and white rice
Which one has more calories?
Of course it's rice
It's rice
White rice per 100g
It has 183 kilocalories.
Potatoes only have 77 calories
White rice has over 100 more calories than potatoes.
Is it a lot different?
yes
Want to control calories
Or those who are worried about high blood sugar
There is another trick for you
You let the potatoes cool before eating them
It produces
more resistant starch
Blood sugar rises
30% slower
Is this a plus?
Very good
For those who want to lose weight now
only eat potatoes?
Don't need to eat white rice?
no
Although potatoes are low in calories
they are also nutritious.
But
You can only supplement B vitamins
by eating white rice
You can eat two alternately
Controlling calories
The same applies to the nutrients that should be supplemented
Eat well and be full
Muscle Cramps Are No Small Matter! Eat This Way to Replenish Potassium and Prevent Pain
Beautiful wife
Have you ever had such an experience?
Not warming up before exercise
Or you get a leg cramp
while exercising.
That pain
It's like being electrocuted.
can't even stand up
Yes
It hurts so much that the whole person jumps up
Others
He slept until midnight
Sudden leg cramp
It hurts so much
What if you have this situation?
Can be supplemented
The two minerals, potassium and magnesium.
Can help you
Relax your muscles
Stabilize your blood pressure
Improve blood circulation
you like sports
eat bananas after exercise
to supplement potassium
Eating potatoes is also useful
100 grams of potatoes
Contains 335 mg of potassium
There is also magnesium, which helps muscles relax
Share a
Delicious and healthy food
Three-color beans, potatoes and shredded pork
When I was studying in the United States
Often with roommates
Let’s make this delicious dish together
The prepared materials are
100g tricolor beans
1 potato
100 grams of pork tenderloin, diced
A little chopped green onion
1 tsp soy sauce
1 tsp salt
½ tsp oyster sauce
1 tsp sesame oil
1 tsp pepper
First, cook the tenderloin with a little salt and oil
Marinate and reserve for later use
Get another pot
After heating the pot
Pour 1 tablespoon of oil
Stir-fry the pork tenderloin until it turns white
About 30 seconds
Add diced potatoes and tri-color beans
Fry together for about 5 minutes
Add soy sauce, oyster sauce, salt and pepper
Stir-fry with sesame oil
Wait until the aroma comes out
Sprinkle chopped green onions, then remove from the pan and plate
If there is no chopped green onion at home
It doesn't matter if you don't add
This dish is sweet
The colors look colorful too
That's how beautiful it looks.
The children saw
also like to eat
Yes
You are a person who often gets cramps
Steamed potatoes are also good
Steaming
can retain more nutrients
Eat a little after exercise
Supplement energy and potassium
Eating Sprouted Potatoes by Mistake Can Be Fatal — 2 Tips to Prevent Potatoes from Sprouting
The editor said his mom last time
To cook curry potatoes
When preparing food
Discovering potatoes
There are actually sprouts growing on it
The editor's mom is very hardworking and frugal in managing the household.
feel the place where sprout
Just cut it off and it's done, right?
Okay, cook it as usual.
這樣不行喔
Yes
Potato sprouting is not a small matter
It produces a
Natural poison: solanine
The concentration will be higher after germination.
More than five times higher
than normal potatoes
Don't think it's peeled or cooked.
This will solve the problem
solanine
Will spread throughout the potato
Accidentally eat it
If the symptoms are mild
Vomiting Abdominal pain
Severe cases may lead to
Heart failure
or respiratory center paralysis.
And death
It's okay
I have a secret trick
Can prevent potatoes from sprouting
Share it with us now
It's very simple
Put the potatoes and apples
Apple is Apple
Putting it all together
If there isn't any,
You just cover the potatoes
with a piece of cloth
Don't expose to the sun
Keep in a cool place
This way, it won’t sprout.
Great
That's what my beautiful wife said
Learn it now
Sweet Potato vs. Potato: How to Choose for Weight Loss and Heart Health
You said potatoes are good
What about sweet potatoes?
But now people who lose weight
They also eat sweet potatoes
This is a very good question.
In fact,
they each have their own advantages
The key is
What effect do you want to achieve?
What if you want to lose weight?
Eat potatoes
Potato calories
Lower than sweet potatoes
Per 100g potato
Only 77 calories
Sweet potatoes have 130 calories.
So choose potatoes
It's quite good
So that's how it is
Is it better for people with constipation
to eat sweet potatoes?
That's right
Sweet potatoes are high in dietary fiber
It helps with bowel movements.
What about protecting blood vessels?
Vitamin C is important for protecting blood vessels
Vitamin C in potatoes
Its content is higher than that of sweet potatoes
30 mg per 100 g
1.2 times that of sweet potato
Vitamin C
helps blood vessels maintain elasticity
Prevent blood vessel blockage
Delaying vascular dementia
So people who want to lose weight
and protect blood vessels
Choose potatoes
Choose sweet potatoes to protect your stomach
Want to see more exciting content?
Welcome to leave a message about your favorite topic
We will read your message.
Thank you